Council 82 Security and Law Enforement Employees, AFSCME; Records apap066
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Council 82, Security and Law Enforcement Employees, American Federation of State, County, Municipal Employees Records
1966-1989
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
apap066
9.6 cubic ft. 1 Microfilm Reels
This collection documents the day-to-day activities of Council 82, the New York State Law Enforcement Officers Union, during its first two decades of existence.
Biographical History
Council 82 was formed through the merger of two unions, Councils 30 and 50. Council 30, when it began, solicited the membership of all state employees. The corrections officers decided Council 30 had neglected its duty to bargain in good faith for them and opted to establish their own union to, address more fully the rigors of their profession. In 1953, members of the Correction Officers Association (COA) negotiated with the corrections employees of Council 30 to organize their own separate union. The 662 COA members from eight prisons formed what would become Council 50. On September 3, 1969 correctional employees from Council 50 and Council 30 consolidated their efforts and formed Council 82. The union's first contract with New York State was signed In 1970.
Council 82, like other unions, lobbied the state to Increase wages and benefits but more Importantly to increase support staff throughout the state's overcrowded correctional facilities. In September 1971 a riot at the Attica Correctional Facility in Attica, New York left 11 corrections officers and 32 inmates dead. Council 82 used the incident at Attica to petition the state for more satisfactory working conditions and an increase in staff.
In April 1979, 6,400 corrections employees went on strike for 16 days. Council 82 was fined $2.5 million for contempt of court under New York's Taylor Law. The fine was later reduced to $150,000 which the court allowed to be paid in monthly installments so as to permit the union to continue operations. Council 82 also lost its privilege of dues check-off for three months as a result of the strike.
Council 82 experienced two other major hostage crises. The first was the Ossining takeover. In January 1983, 600 inmates in Cell Block B took 19 corrections officers hostage for 53 hours. Council 82 experienced its last major hostage crisis on August 1, 1988. Five corrections officers were taken hostage at the Coxsackie Correctional Facility. The officers were released, unharmed, the next day.
In 1984 The Union of Federated Corrections Officers (TUFCO) challenged Council 82 as the exclusive representative of the state's Security and Law Enforcement Employees. An election was held so that members could vote for the representative of their choice. On February 22, 1985 the Public Employment Relations Board (PERB) announced Council 82's victory over the T.U.F.C.O. association.
Council 82 Is the exclusive bargaining representative of over 22,000 Security and Law Enforcement employees. With the exception of the State Police, Council 82 represents all New York State law enforcement personnel.
Scope and Contents
The records of Council 82 document every year of the organization's existence with minutes, newspapers, and other material. Council 82's records are divided into six series: Executive Board Files, 1969,1972-86; Subject Files, 1968-87; Legal Files, 1976-84; T.U.F.C.O. Files, 1983-87; Sing Sing Local 1413, Records, 1972-80; and Council 82 Newspapers, 1971, 1974, 1980-89.
Council 82 was one of the first and became one of the largest and most important of the public sector unions to organize after the implementation of the Taylor Law. The records of Council 82 document how a large union organized itself at the state level and initiated a dialogue with the state of New York. One of the most important activities of Council 82 has been to negotiate contracts with the state, and minutes, newspapers, and subject files, each in different ways, elucidate the procedures and accomplishments of these negotiations.
The most extensive series is the Executive Board files, which contain correspondence and minutes of Executive Board meetings and which give a good idea of the activities of the union during almost its entire history. This series documents the entire range of Council 82's activities: political action, lobbying, and relations with the state and other unions. The other series give more detailed information on some activities of Council 82. The newspapers, for example, are the public voice of Council 82 and the clearest indication of the union's opinion about corrections policy and other matters.
The records of Sing Sing Local 1413 are records that were transferred to Council 82 when Local 1413 closed down. These are the only records that were not produced by the statewide union itself.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized into the following series: 1 - Executive Board Files: 1969, 1972-1986; 2 - Subject Files: 1968-1987; 3 - Legal Files: 1976-1984; 4 - T.U.F.C.O. (The Union of Federated Corrections Officers) Files: 1983-1987; 5 - Sing Sing Local 1413: 1972-1980; Series 6 - Council 82 Newspapers: 1971, 1974, 1980-1989.
Acquisition Information
Council 82, Security and Law Enforcement Employees, AFSCME donated these records to the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted with the exception of Series 3.
Labor; Criminal Justice and Prisons; Correctional personnel--New York (State); Prison administration--New York (State); Government employee unions--New York (State); Minutes; Contracts; Newsletters; AFSCME--Council 82 (N.Y.)
- Executive Board Files, 1969-1986; 1; 1.4 cubic ft.
  Scope and Contents
  Contains minutes of executive board meetings (1969, 1972-86) and correspondence relating to those meetings (1978-86). The Executive Board Files were maintained as a record of the activities of the organization as well a record of correspondence between the organization, its members, and the public. Although Council 82 began in 1968 the Executive Board Files do not begin until 1969. There is a gap of two years (1970-71) in the meeting minutes. Executive Board files produced after 1986 are In the possession of Council 82.
  - Meeting Notices, 1973-1977 (Box 1 (1-Executive Board Files), Folder 1)
  - Meeting Notices, 1979-1984 (Box 1 (1-Executive Board Files), Folder 2)
  - Minutes, 1969 (Box 1 (1-Executive Board Files), Folder 3)
  - Minutes, 1972 (Box 1 (1-Executive Board Files), Folder 4)
  - Minutes, 1973 (Box 1 (1-Executive Board Files), Folder 5)
  - Minutes, 1974 (Box 1 (1-Executive Board Files), Folder 6)
  - Minutes, 1975 (Box 1 (1-Executive Board Files), Folder 7)
  - Minutes, 1976 (Box 1 (1-Executive Board Files), Folder 8)
  - Minutes, 1977 (Box 1 (1-Executive Board Files), Folder 9)
  - Minutes, 1978 (Box 1 (1-Executive Board Files), Folder 10)
  - Minutes, 1978 (Box 1 (1-Executive Board Files), Folder 11)
  - Minutes, 1979 (Box 1 (1-Executive Board Files), Folder 12)
  - Minutes, 1980 (Box 1 (1-Executive Board Files), Folder 13)
  - Minutes, 1981 (Box 1 (1-Executive Board Files), Folder 14)
  - Minutes, 1982 (Box 1 (1-Executive Board Files), Folder 15)
  - Minutes, 1983 (Box 1 (1-Executive Board Files), Folder 16)
  - Minutes, 1984 (Box 1 (1-Executive Board Files), Folder 17)
  - Minutes, 1985 (Box 1 (1-Executive Board Files), Folder 18)
  - Minutes, 1987 (Box 1 (1-Executive Board Files), Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 1 (1-Executive Board Files), Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 1 (1-Executive Board Files), Folder 21)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1982 (Box 1 (1-Executive Board Files), Folder 22)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1982 (Box 1 (1-Executive Board Files), Folder 23)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1983 (Box 1 (1-Executive Board Files), Folder 24)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1983 (Box 1 (1-Executive Board Files), Folder 25)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 1 (1-Executive Board Files), Folder 26)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 1 (1-Executive Board Files), Folder 27)
  - Correspondence (1 of 5), 1984 (Box 2 (1-Executive Board Files), Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (2 of 5), 1984 (Box 2 (1-Executive Board Files), Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (3 of 5), 1984 (Box 2 (1-Executive Board Files), Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (4 of 5), 1984 (Box 2 (1-Executive Board Files), Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (5 of 5), 1984 (Box 2 (1-Executive Board Files), Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1985 (Box 2 (1-Executive Board Files), Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1985 (Box 2 (1-Executive Board Files), Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 2 (1-Executive Board Files), Folder 8)
- Subject Files, 1968-1987; 2; 3.0 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically.
  Contains annual conventions (1970-81), contract negotiations (1969-70), minutes of the Correction Policy Committee (1968-78), and minutes of meetings of local presidents' (1981, 1983-85). The subject files are a record of the activities of Council 82, the bulk of the series consisting of annual convention minutes, Correction Policy Committee correspondence and minutes, and correspondence with the Department of Correctional Services. Conspicuously absent from the files is documentation on the 1971 riot at the Attica Correctional Facility in Attica, New York. Similarly, there is little documentation pertaining to the strike of 1979 during which 6,400 corrections employees went on strike for 16 days.
  - American Corrections Association, 1984 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - American Corrections Association Convention, 1983 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - American Correctional Association, 1982-1984 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Annual Convention--First, 1970 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Annual Convention--Second, 1971 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Annual Convention-Third (special), 1972 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Annual Convention--Fourth, 1972 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Annual Convention-Fifth, 1973 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Annual Convention-Sixth, 1974 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Annual Convention--Seventh, 1975 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Annual Convention--Eighth, 1976 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Annual Convention--Ninth, 1977 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Annual Convention-Tenth, 1978 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Annual Convention--Eleventh, 1979 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Annual Convention--Twelfth (1 of 2), 1980 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Annual Convention--Twelfth (2 of 2), 1980 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Annual Convention-Thirteenth (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Annual Convention-Thirteenth (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Collective Bargaining Agreements, 1972-1974; 1977-1979 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Commission of Correction, 1975-1979 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Campaign Material, 1984 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Conservation--Preservation Employees, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Constitution, 1975-1983 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Constitution Amendments and Resolutions, 1979 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Contract Agreement, 1984-1987 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Contract Demands--Statewide and Departmental, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Contract Negotiations, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Contract Negotiations, 1970 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Contract Negotiations--Minutes, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Contract with New York State, 1985 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Convention Report, 1980 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Convention Report--Amendments Rules, 1985 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Correction Officer (Draft of Dissertation) (1 of 2), 1977 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Correction Officer (Draft of Dissertation) (2 of 2), 1977 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Corrections Officers Benefit Association, 1978 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Correction Policy Committee--Correspondence and Minutes, 1968 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Correction Policy Committee--Correspondence and Minutes, 1968-1969 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Correction Policy Committee--Correspondence and Minutes, 1969-1970 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Correction Policy Committee--Correspondence and Minutes, 1973 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Correction Policy Committee--Correspondence and Minutes, 1974 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Correction Policy Committee--Correspondence and Minutes, 1975 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Correction Policy Commfttee--Correspondence and Minutes, 1976 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Correction Policy Committee--Correspondence and Minutes, 1977 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Correction Policy Committee--Correspondence and Minutes, 1978 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Correction Policy Committee--Correspondence and Minutes, 1980 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Correction Policy Committee--Correspondence and Minutes, 1982 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Correction Policy Committee--Correspondence and Minutes, 1983 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Correction Policy Committee--Correspondence and Minutes, 1984 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Correction Locals' Correspondence, 1972-1978 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Correspondence of Council 50, 1969-1970 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Correspondence to Executive Directors, 1980 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - CSEA, 1974-1979 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Comptroller's Advisory Council, 1976 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Council 66, 1972-1978 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Department of Correctional Services, 1971 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Department of Correctional Services, 1972 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Department of Correctional Services, 1973 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Department of Correctional Services, 1974 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Department of Correctional Services, 1975 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Department of Correctional Services, 1976 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Department of Correctional Services, 1977 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Department of Correctional Services--Directives, 1984 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Department of Correctional Services--Employee Manual, 1977 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Department of Correctional Services, 1978 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Department of Correctional Services, 1979 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Department of Correctional Services, 1980-1981 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Department of Correctional Services, 1982 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Employee Assistance Program, 1980 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Employee Health Insurance, 1972 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Expense Voucher, 1978 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Grievances--Downstate Local 399, 1979-1981 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Grievance-Great Meadow Local 1279, 1975-1978 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Handbook for Employees and Supervisors, 1980 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Improper Practice--Certification Election, 1979 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Insurance Committee Meeting, 1979 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Job Performance Appraisals, 1968 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Labor/Management Meeting Minutes--Local, 1979-1980 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Labor/Management Meeting Minutes--Local, 1981 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Labor/Management Meeting Minutes--Statewide, 1983-1984 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Legislative Chairman File, 1981-1982 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Local President's Meeting Minutes, 1981 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Local President's Meeting Minutes, 1983 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Local President's Meeting Minutes, 1984 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Local President's Meeting Minutes, 1985 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Merger Agreements, 1969 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - News Releases, 1979-1980 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - News Releases, 1980-1982 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - News Releases, 1983-1984 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Newspaper Clippings (1 of 2), 1980-1981 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Newspaper Clippings (2 of 2), 1980-1981 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Office of Employee Relations--Arbitrations, 1980 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Office of Employee Relations--Correspondence, 1980 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Public Employment Relations Board, 1984 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Quality of Working Life Committee, 1983 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Quality of Working Life Committee--Aprrovals, 1983 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Quality of Working Life Committee--Disapprovals, 1983 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Quality of Working Life Committee--Meeting, 1983 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Security Unit Employee's Council, 1969 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Sing Sing-Local 1413, 1983 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Staff Meetings, 1984-1985 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Staff Meetings--Notes, 1983-1985 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Staff Reports From Locals, 1983-1984 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Village of Catskill, 1983-1984 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 41)
- Legal Files, 1976-1984; 3; 4.0 cubic ft.
  Contains affidavits (1979-82), notices of hearing (1979-81), notices of determination (1981-82)), grievance arbitrations (1983-84). The Legal Files spanning only eight years, form the largest series. Most of the series is devoted to the Strike of 1979 during which 6,400 corrections employees went on strike for 16 days. Included In the 1979 Strike records are affidavits, notices of hearing, and notices of determination. In addition to strike information there are also grievance arbitrations and decisions relating to sex discrimination and disciplinary grievances.
  - Council 82 v. NYS Department of Correctional Services, Affidavit of Service, 1983 (Box 1 (3-Legal Files), Folder 1)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Must consult archivist before viewing this material.
  - Council 82 v. NYS Department of Correctional Services, Arbitration Award, 1977 (Box 1 (3-Legal Files), Folder 2)
  - Council 82 v. NYS Department of Correctional Services, Arbitration Award, 1982 (Box 1 (3-Legal Files), Folder 3)
  - Richard Egger, Grievance v. NYS Department of Correctional Services, Grievance Arbitration, 1982 (Box 1 (3-Legal Files), Folder 4)
  - Richard Egger, Grievance v. NYS Department of Correctional Services, Grievance Arbitration, 1983 (Box 1 (3-Legal Files), Folder 5)
  - Richard Egger, Grievance v. NYS Department of Correctional Services, Grievance Arbitration, 1984 (Box 1 (3-Legal Files), Folder 6)
  - Richard Egger, Grievance v. NYS Department of Correctional Services, Notice of Petition, 1983 (Box 1 (3-Legal Files), Folder 7)
  - Grievance--Albion Correctional Facility, 1980 (Box 1 (3-Legal Files), Folder 8)
  - Thomas Page, Grievance v. State University of New York, Disciplinary Grievance Arbitration (1 of 5), 1982 (Box 1 (3-Legal Files), Folder 9)
  - Thomas Page, Grievance v. State University of New York, Disciplinary Grievance Arbitration (2 of 5), 1982 (Box 1 (3-Legal Files), Folder 10)
  - Thomas Page, Grievance v. State University of New York, Disciplinary Grievance Arbitration (3 of 5), 1982 (Box 1 (3-Legal Files), Folder 11)
  - Thomas Page, Grievance v. State University of New York, Disciplinary Grievance Arbitration (4 of 5), 1982 (Box 1 (3-Legal Files), Folder 12)
  - Thomas Page, Grievance v. State University of New York, Disciplinary Grievance Arbitration (5 of 5), 1982 (Box 1 (3-Legal Files), Folder 13)
  - Office of Employee Relations, 1981 (Box 1 (3-Legal Files), Folder 14)
  - Notice of Petition, 1981-1983 (Box 1 (3-Legal Files), Folder 15)
  - Iola Forts v. Benjamin Ward, Court Exhibits, 1977 (Box 1 (3-Legal Files), Folder 16)
  - Sex Discrimination in Employment--Albion Correctional Facility, 1978 (Box 1 (3-Legal Files), Folder 17)
  - Gant & Guarino v. NYS Department of Correctional Services, Sex Discrimination in Employment (1 of 3), 1982 (Box 1 (3-Legal Files), Folder 18)
  - Gant & Guarino v. NYS Department of Correctional Services, Sex Discrimination in Employment (2 of 3), 1982 (Box 1 (3-Legal Files), Folder 19)
  - Gant & Guarino v. NYS Department of Correctional Services, Sex Discrimination in Employment (3 of 3), 1982 (Box 1 (3-Legal Files), Folder 20)
  - Gant & Guarino v. NYS Department of Correctional Services, State Division of Human Rights Hearing, 1982 (Box 1 (3-Legal Files), Folder 21)
  - Jose Garcia v. Robert Abrams, Order and Judgment, 1983 (Box 1 (3-Legal Files), Folder 22)
  - Guarino v. Village of Geneseo, Guarino Affidavit, 1983 (Box 1 (3-Legal Files), Folder 23)
  - AFSCME, Council 82 v. Village of Geneseo, Award of Arbitrator, 1982 (Box 1 (3-Legal Files), Folder 24)
  - AFSCME, Council 82 v. Village of Geneseo, Brief for Charging Party, 1981 (Box 1 (3-Legal Files), Folder 25)
  - AFSCME, Council 82 v. Village of Geneseo, Briefs, 1982 (Box 1 (3-Legal Files), Folder 26)
  - AFSCME, Council 82 v. Village of Geneseo, Correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box 1 (3-Legal Files), Folder 27)
  - AFSCME, Council 82 v. Village of Geneseo, Decision and Order, 1982 (Box 1 (3-Legal Files), Folder 28)
  - AFSCME, Council 82 v. Village of Geneseo, Depositions, 1981 (Box 1 (3-Legal Files), Folder 29)
  - AFSCME, Council 82 v. Village of Geneseo, Exceptions and Request for Oral Agreement, 1981 (Box 1 (3-Legal Files), Folder 30)
  - AFSCME, Council 82 v. Village of Geneseo, Grievance Forms, 1982 (Box 1 (3-Legal Files), Folder 31)
  - AFSCME, Council 82 v. Village of Geneseo, Correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box 1 (3-Legal Files), Folder 32)
  - AFSCME, Council 82 v. Village of Geneseo, Jurisdictional Statement, 1983 (Box 1 (3-Legal Files), Folder 33)
  - AFSCME, Council 82 v. Village of Geneseo, Mac Arthur Affidavit, 1982 (Box 1 (3-Legal Files), Folder 34)
  - AFSCME, Council 82 v. Village of Geneseo, Maloney Affidavit, 1981 (Box 1 (3-Legal Files), Folder 35)
  - AFSCME, Council 82 v. Village of Geneseo, Notice of Appeal, 1982 (Box 1 (3-Legal Files), Folder 36)
  - AFSCME, Council 82 v. Village of Geneseo, Notice of Motion, 1982 (Box 1 (3-Legal Files), Folder 37)
  - NYS PERB v. Village of Geneseo, Notice of Petition, 1982 (Box 2 (3-Legal Files), Folder 1)
  - NYS PERB v. Village of Geneseo, Reply Affidavit, 1982 (Box 2 (3-Legal Files), Folder 2)
  - AFSCME, Council 82 v. Village of Geneseo, Orders, 1982 (Box 2 (3-Legal Files), Folder 3)
  - AFSCME, Council 82 v. Village of Geneseo, Order to Show Cause, 1981 (Box 2 (3-Legal Files), Folder 4)
  - AFSCME, Council 82 v. Village of Geneseo, Petitioner's Brief, 1981 (Box 2 (3-Legal Files), Folder 5)
  - AFSCME, Council 82 v. Village of Geneseo, Record on Appeal, 1982 (Box 2 (3-Legal Files), Folder 6)
  - AFSCME, Council 82 v. Village of Geneseo, Related Cases, 1982 (Box 2 (3-Legal Files), Folder 7)
  - AFSCME, Council 82 v. Village of Geneseo, Respondent's Briefs, 1981 (Box 2 (3-Legal Files), Folder 8)